

### Education

Bina Nusantara University

### **Bachelor of Computer Science**

### Contact

- +62 857 7698 2367
- florianasho@gmail.com
- in Floriana Sho

# Languages

Indonesia (Native)

English

## **Skills**

React|S

VueJS

GraphQL

NextJS

Codelgniter

**HTML** 

CSS

TypeScript

Tailwind

Bootstrap

# Floriana

#### FRONTEND DEVELOPER

### **About Me**

Experienced in Frontend Developer for 6 years. Passionate in Frontend Developer and a fast learner. Interested in finding solutions to make a website user-friendly. Working very well both as a team player or as an individual and able to manage work on time. Most of my experiences are in Frontend Development area which bring me opportunities as a leader of the Frontend teams.

# **Work Experience**

### Sirclo / Nov 2022 - Aug 2023

### **Software Engineer (Frontend Developer)**

Joined the Sirclo Store team and responsible in creating custom website for Sirclo's clients. In developing the website, I used ReactJS, NextJS, GraphQL, TypeScript, and SCSS.

#### Orami / Nov 2019 - Nov 2022

### **Software Engineer (Frontend Developer)**

Joined the B2B team and responsible in creating bulk store marketplace and maintain the website, also creating seller page website. For creating this website, I used React JS, Redux, Next JS, and SCSS.

#### Onero Solution / Jan 2018 - Nov 2019

### **Lead Frontend Developer**

Responsible in developing website and mobile apps, help the UI/UX Designer reviewing the display to make it user-friendly. Moreover, I also responsible to lead the Frontend team by discussing the programming tools and resolving problems faced by the team. Programming tools I used include HTML, CSS, VueJS, Javascript, JQuery, VueQuasar, PHP, and Codelgniter.

# Freelance

Doing website development freelance since 2020. Until now, I developed 4 websites, namely Cherish Academy school website, company profile website for PT. Aneka Kaoline Utama, Mata Investments, and website for publishing company, Cherish Publisher. Each project usually takes 2 weeks until 2 months, depending on its difficulty and website's pages. The development tools used for the project includes Codelgniter and Bootstrap.